[Music]
long no
small pretty and
Y cuz my paper long it's a Friday night
Ain i p my shots cuz drink I'm outside
again I home it's giv
her
face
face s e s
y come on rock
[Music]
out the lime in the cook P up put the
lime in the Cook Dr f up the lime in the
C Dr f up the lime in the she the up
[Music]
a little bit I H the stage I'm hearing
it it's black star black feeling
[Music]
night I Ain home I P my shots cuz I
drink I'm outside again
hat it's giving her
face
[Music]
face call baby
do you dance how
baby I'm
on no party man sh the plug again she
take off man I see a
[Music]
with come on
come on
[Music]
[Applause]
sh this
[Music]
B they me like I
[Applause]
[Music]
l
shots Call
Me Baby you you
you hey
[Music]
come e
m e m
[Music]
m
no
[Music]
I l
I
[Music]
sh